Guide to the Undergraduate Affairs, Yale College, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the Associate Dean for Student Affairs, 1969-1990; Accession 1990-A-157
  - Joint Council of Social Chairmen (JCSC)
    - Mailing Lists, Student Requests for, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Minority Advisory Council (MAC)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Subcommittee on Prop, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Minority Recruitment Program, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Minority Student Graduate School Name Exchange
    - 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - 1986 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - 1987 (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - 1988 (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - New England Deans' Association, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - News Paper Delivery Agency, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Old Campus Housing, Housing of Athletes, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - Old Campus Security Problems, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Old Campus: General, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Opening Days of School, Report on, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Police Advisory Board, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Police Reports
    - 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - University Policy on Political Campaign Activities at Yale, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - Poster Regulations, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - President's Harassment Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Public Speaking Competition, Undergraduate
    - 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - 1984 (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - 1985 (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - 1986 (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - 1987 Apr 25-26 (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - 1988 Apr 19-20 (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - Residential Colleges, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Request for Services, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Retirement Advisory Committee, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - Security, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Security, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Senior Class, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - Senior Class Elections, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - Senior Class Elections, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - Senior Profile Study, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - Senior Societies Coalition, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - Sigma Pi Phi Fraternity, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 157)
  - Social Activities Committee (SAC)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - Fee Credit for Cultural Centers, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - Fee Credit for Cultural Centers, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - Minority Group, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - Space Allocations, Undergraduate Organizations, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - Space Allocations, Undergraduate Organizations, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - Student Census: Residential Colleges, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - Student Life Committee, 1972, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 166)
    - Student Records and Systems, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 167)
    - Table Tent Policy, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 168)
    - Task Force, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 169)
    - Theatre Studies: Wall St. Chamber Players, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 171)
    - Timothy Dwight Annex Space, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 172)
    - Truman Fellowships, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 173)
    - Tyco, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 174)
    - Undergraduate Organizations, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 175)
    - Undergraduate Regulations, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 176)
    - Undergraduate Regulations, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 177)
    - Urban Improvement Corps, Inc., 1983 (Box 3, Folder 178)
    - Urban Improvement Corps, Inc., 1984 (Box 3, Folder 179)
    - West Point Conference, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 180)
    - Winter Recess, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 181)
    - Yale College Council Summer Mailing, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 182)
    - Yale College Council Summer Mailing, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 183)
    - Yale Free Press, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 184)
    - Yale Gay/Lesbian Co-operative, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - Undergraduate Organizations
    - A.I.E.S.E.C., 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 186)
    - Amateur Radio Club, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 187)
    - American Field Service (AFS) Club, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    - Asian American Student Organization (AASA), 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 189)
    - Association of Yale Alumni (AYA) Student-Alumni Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 190)
    - Aurelian Honor Society, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 191)
    - Bach Society, Yale, 1984-1987 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    - Ballroom Dance Club, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 193)
    - Baptist Student Union, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 194)
    - Beyond War Project, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 195)
    - Black Student Alliance at Yale (BSAY), 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 196)
    - Business and Economic Forum, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 197)
    - Canadian Students at Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 198)
    - Caribbean Club at Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 199)
    - Cheerleading Squad, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 200)
    - Chess Club at Yale, Undergraduate, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 201)
    - Christian Fellowship, Yale (YCF), 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 202)
    - Charities Drive, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 203)
    - Clan na Gael, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 204)
    - Coalition Against Apartheid, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 205)
    - Coalition for an Educated Choice, Yale, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 206)
    - Coalition for the Homeless, Yale Student, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 207)
    - College Colloquium, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 208)
    - College Council, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 209)
    - College Democrats, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 210)
    - College Republicans, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 211)
    - College Student Investment Group, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 212)
    - Committee for Freedom, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 213)
    - Community of Women Athletes, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 214)
    - Communiversity Day, Students for, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 215)
    - Debate Association, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 216)
    - Democratic Socialists of America, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 217)
    - Despierta Boricua, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 218)
    - Dramatic Association, Yale University, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 219)
    - Dwight Hall Student Cabinet, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 220)
    - Equal Access for Students at Yale, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 221)
    - Exit Players, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 222)
    - Fall Festival Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 223)
    - Fifth Dimension: A Yale Science Fiction Society, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 224)
    - Film Production, Yale Students, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 225)
    - Freshman Outdoor Orientation Trips (FOOT), 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 226)
    - Freshwomen's Alliance, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 227)
    - Gays, Bisexuals and Lesbians of Color, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 228)
    - Gay Students' Center at Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 229)
    - Global Forum, Yale Undergraduate, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 230)
    - Heritage Theatre Ensemble, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 231)
    - Hillel Student Council, Yale, 1988-90 (Box 4, Folder 232)
    - Hunger Action Project, Yale (YHAP), 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 233)
    - Institute of Electrical and Electronic Engineers, Yale University Student Chapter, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 234)
    - Interactions / Society Organized Against Racism (SOAR), 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 235)
    - International Relations Association / Model United Nations Conference, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 236)
    - Joint Council of Social Chairs (JCSC), 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 237)
    - Korean-American Students of Yale College, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 238)
    - Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Co-op at Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 239)
    - Liberal Party of the Political Union, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 240)
    - The Men's Caucus, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 241)
    - Mime Troupe, Yale, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 242)
    - Mountaineering Club, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 243)
    - Movement Opposed to Violence and Extortion, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 244)
    - Movimiento Estudiantil Chicano de Aztlan, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 245)
    - New Haven Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 246)
    - New Haven/Leon Sister City Project, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 247)
    - New Internationalist Society, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 248)
    - Nichiren Soshu Student Group, 1984-1988 (Box 4, Folder 249)
    - Nuclear Disarmament, Yale Students for, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 250)
    - Objectivism Study Group, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 251)
    - Orthodox Christian Fellowship at Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 252)
    - Outdoor Corps, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 253)
    - Outing Club, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 254)
    - Party of the Right, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 255)
    - Political Union, Yale, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 256)
    - Polytechnic Preparatory School Club, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 257)
    - Progressive Zionist Caucus, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 258)
    - Purple Crayon of Yale: An Undergraduate Improvisational Acting Troupe, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 259)
    - Recycling, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 260)
    - Republican Mainstream at Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 261)
    - Response, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 262)
    - Sanctuary Project, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 263)
    - Secular Humanist Discussion Group, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 264)
    - South Asian Society (SAS), 1983-1987 (Box 4, Folder 265)
    - Speak, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 266)
    - Student Animal Rights Coalition (SARC), 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 267)
    - Student Bridge Club, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 268)
    - Student Chapter of Amnesty International, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 269)
    - Student Chapter of Campus Crusade for Christ, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 270)
    - Student Danceworks at Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 271)
    - Student Environment Coalition, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 272)
    - Student Friends of Israel, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 273)
    - Student Gynecological Resources, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 274)
    - Student Pan-American Society, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 275)
    - Student Pugwash at Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 276)
    - Student Speech Association, Yale (Formerly the Yale Society for Creative Discourse), 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 277)
    - Student Study of God, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 278)
    - Students for Islamic Awareness, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 279)
    - Students for Life, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 280)
    - Sub Rosa, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 281)
    - Tory Party, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 282)
    - Trips for Outdoor Enjoyment (TOE), 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 283)
    - Undergraduate Art Gallery, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 284)
    - Undergraduate Computer Science Organization, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 285)
    - Undergraduate Economics Group, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 286)
    - Undergraduate Schools Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 287)
    - United Assembly of European Students, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 288)
    - University Pictures, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 289)
    - Video Yearbook, Yale Student Production, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 290)
    - Walden: Student to Student Counseling, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 291)
    - Wall St. Festival Organizing Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 292)
    - Wall St. Festival Organizing Committee Finances, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 293)
    - Women's Caucus, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 294)
    - Women's Center Resource, Yale Undergraduate, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 295)
    - Women's Open Forum, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 296)
    - Yale-China Association, Student Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 297)
    - Yale Dancers, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 298)
    - Yalesbians, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 299)
    - Young Israel House at Yale, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 300)
    - Youth Together, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 301)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha Fraternity, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 302)
    - Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 303)
    - Kappa Alpha Theta, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 304)
    - Kappa Alpha Psi, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 305)
    - Kappa Kappa Gamma, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 306)
    - Pan-Hellenic Association, Undergraduate, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 307)
    - Sigma Chi (Old Campus Association), 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 308)
    - Berkeley People's Film Society, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 309)
    - Ezra Stiles Film Society, 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 310)
    - Spectrum Film Society, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 311)
    - The Alliance, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 312)
    - Aurora Magazine, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 313)
    - Banner Publications, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 314)
    - Black and White: The Yale Undergraduate Photographic Journal, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 315)
    - Economics and Business Review, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 316)
    - Daily News, Inc. Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 317)
    - Undergraduate Course Critique, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 318)
    - Herald, The Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 319)
    - New Journal, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 320)
    - Political Monthly, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 321)
    - Prism: Undergraduate Journal, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 322)
    - Record, The Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 323)
    - Rhetorician, Yale: Student Forum, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 324)
    - Ritual and Dissent, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 325)
    - Scientific Publications, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 326)
    - Standard, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 327)
    - Urim V'tumim: A Jewish Undergraduate Quarterly at Yale, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 328)
    - Vernacular, The Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 329)
    - Women of the Ivy League Magazine, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 330)
    - The Yale: A Student Guide to Yale and New Haven, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 331)
    - Alley Cats, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 332)
    - Duke"s Men of Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 333)
    - Mixed Company, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 334)
    - The New Blue, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 335)
    - Nuova Musica, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 336)
    - Out of the Blue, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 337)
    - Proof of the Pudding, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 338)
    - Russian Chorus, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 339)
    - Slavic Chorus, Yale, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 340)
    - Society of Orpheus and Bacchus, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 341)
    - Whim 'n' Rhythm, 1984-1987 (Box 4, Folder 342)
    - Housing, 1976-1981 (Box 5, Folder 343)
  - Old Campus
    - Floor Plans and Room Census, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 344)
    - Floor Plans by Room, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 345)
    - Housing, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 346)
    - Report on the Feasibility of Housing All Freshmen on the Old Campus, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 347)
    - Housing Assignments, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 348)
    - Housing Assignments, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 349)
    - Housing Assignments, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 350)
    - Freshmen Housing, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 351)
    - Freshmen Housing Printout, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 352)
    - Housing, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 353)
    - Old Campus Housing Assignments, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 354)
    - Old Campus Housing Assignments, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 355)
    - Yale College Freshman Roster, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 356)
    - Coded Room List, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 357)
    - Housing: Off-Campus Annex Problems, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 358)
    - Off-Campus Annexes, 1977-1980 (Box 5, Folder 359)
    - Annex Housing, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 360)
    - Off-Campus Annexes, Housing, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 361)
    - Housing, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 362)
    - Upperclassmen, Off-Campus Housing, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 363)
    - Old Campus Annex Housing, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 364)
    - Old Campus Housing: Responses to Memorandum to College, 1977-1983 (Box 5, Folder 365)
    - Housing: Off-Campus Annexes, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 366)
    - Steven Course: Residential College Room Draws, 1976 May (Box 5, Folder 367)
    - Ezra Stiles College, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 368)
    - Pierson College, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 369)
    - Trumbull College, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 370)
    - Saybrook College, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 371)
    - Building Maintenance, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 372)
    - Housing Conference Agenda, 1980 Spring (Box 5, Folder 373)
    - Housing Freshmen Admits, 1982 May (Box 5, Folder 374)
    - Housing Gender Issues, 1978-1983 (Box 5, Folder 375)
    - General Housing Information, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 376)
    - Housing Issues: Correspondence with Other Universities, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 377)
    - Housing: Minority Issues, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 378)
    - Old Campus: Housing Problems, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 379)
    - On-Campus Housing, Relinquishing Policy and Procedure, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 380)
    - Housing Assignments, 1980 Spring (Box 5, Folder 381)
    - Housing Regulations: Title IX, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 382)
    - Housing Report, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 383)
    - Relinquishment Fines Excused, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 384)
    - Wright Hall Emergency Rooms, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 385)
    - Relinquishment Policy, 1978-1983 (Box 5, Folder 386)
    - Floating Counselors, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 387)
    - Floating Counselors, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 388)
    - Winter Recess, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 389)
    - Request to Live Off-Campus Forms, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 390)
    - Committee to Review the State of Minority Students, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 391)
    - Minority Students, Committee to Review the Status of - in Yale College, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 392)
    - Committee to Review Policies and Procedures for Undergraduate Organizations, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 393)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Organizations, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 394)
    - Directories of Undergraduate Organizations, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 395)
    - Black Student Alliance at Yale (BSAY), 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 396)
    - Class of 1981 Freshman Allocations, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 397)
    - Honors and Special Projects, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 398)
    - Room Change Request, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 399)
    - Health Insurance, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 400)
    - Legal, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 401)
    - Joint Council of Social Chairmen (JCSC), 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 402)
    - University Memos, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 403)
    - Movimiento Estudiantil Chicano de Aztlan (M.E.Ch.A.) Master Lists, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 404)
    - M.E.Ch.A. Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 405)
    - Minority Student Development Task Force, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 406)
    - Minority Student / Graduate School Name Exchange, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 407)
    - New England Minority Women Administrators (NEMWA), 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 408)
    - New England Association of Academic Personnel (NEAAP), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 409)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 410)
    - News Releases, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 411)
    - National Hook-up of Black Women, Inc., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 412)
    - Obstretics and Gynecology (Obs-Gyn) Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 413)
    - Obs-Gyn Review Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 414)
    - Police Advisory Board, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 415)
    - Yale Review, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 416)
    - Resource Center on Women in Higher Education, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 417)
    - Summer Term, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 418)
    - Scholar of the House, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 419)
    - Security Memos, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 420)
    - Yale Symphony, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 421)
    - Urban Improvement Corps, Inc. (UIC), 1978 (Box 6, Folder 422)
    - U. S. Grant, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 423)
    - Tutoring Applications, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 424)
    - Yale Band, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 425)
    - Young Men"s Christian Association (YMCA), 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 426)
    - Unrenewed, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 427)
- Records of the Dean of Undergraduate Affairs, Yale College, circa 1955-1986; Accession 1991-A-022
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2022
  - Records of Undergraduate Student Organizations, 1980-1986
    - AIESEC (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Alliance for Sexual Progress (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - American Field Service (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - A Propos (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Assoc. of Yale Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Atlas (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Asian American Students Association (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Aurelian Honor Society (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Aurora Magazine (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Baker's Dozen (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - BLS Students Organization (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Berkeley People's Film Society (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Beyond War Project (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Bicycle Club (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Black Athletes of Yale (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Black Pre-Law Society (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Black Pre-Professional Council (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Black Student Alliance at Yale (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Black Undergraduate Women's Group (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Builders of Peace (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Bulldog Squares (Box 1, Folder 21 - 22)
    - Calliopean Society (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Campaign Against Militarism and the Draft (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Career Options Committee (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Chinese Students Association (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Christian Science Organization (Box 1, Folder 27 - 28)
    - Chug Aliah (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - CIA Out (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Coalition Against Apartheid (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Coalition for Undergraduate Counseling (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Coalition to end the Strike (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - College Council of Dramats (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - College Meditation Group (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador (CISPES) (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Counseling (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Computer Science Group (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Ct. Committee for Handgun Control (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Council of College Councils (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Council on Eating Disorders (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Creative Loafing (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Credo Magazine (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Delta Kappa Epsilon (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Democratic Socialists of America (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Despierta Boricua (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Dialects (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Draft Information Service (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Duke's Men of Yale (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Environmental Advocacy Group (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - ERA Action Committee (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Eurasian Colloquium at Yale (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Experiments (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Ezra Stiles Film Society (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Fellowship of the Game (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Geist Magazine (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Goose and Anvil (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Harkness Tower (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Independent Party of the YPU (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Interminority Action Coalition (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - International Forum at Yale (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Jetsam (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Kappa Sigma Fraternity (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Kochavim: Y. Israeli Dance Ensemble (Box 1, Folder 64 - 65)
    - Korean-American Journal (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Korean American Students Association (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Krisha Yoga Society (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Latin American Study Forum (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Latter-Day Saints Students Association (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Leonardo da Vinci Society (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Little Boxes (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Living Water (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Minority Business Association (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Musical Collective (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - New Blue (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - New Four Piece Electronic Dance Band (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - New Haven Bulletin Board System (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - New Journal (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Newtonians (Box 1, Folder 80)